yupgames.com 2014-04-23

# Privacy Policy on YupGames.com

At YupGames, we respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to our websites need to control the uses of their personal information. YupGames will take all the necessary measures to protect your privacy in connection with your use of the sites owned and operated by YupGames.

Information You Provide to Us

We may collect several types of personal information including your name, email address, age, gender, ip address, etc. All information collected shall remain private and shall not be provided to any 3rd parties unless specifically noted.

Cookies

YupGames.com site also uses cookies. We and other companies may use cookies for a variety of purposes including but not limited to remembering your login information, administration, and tracking purposes. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your web experience smoother, and some of our services may not function properly.

Usage Tracking

YupGames.com uses a variety of technical methods for administration and tracking purposes. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns, such as the frequency users visit various areas of YupGames.com site. These technical methods may involve transmitting information either directly to us or to another entity authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

Network Advertisers

Many advertisements are managed and placed on YupGames.com site by third parties. These companies are called "network advertisers." Network advertisers who place advertisements on YupGames.com site may also use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information when you click on or move your cursor over one of their banner advertisements. You may not realize this information is being collected. In some cases, we may have access to information from web beacons and cookies used by network advertisers on YupGames.com site and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited that are also associated with the network advertiser.

Finally, once you've clicked on an advertisement and have left YupGames.com site, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

Contacting Us

If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can contact us.
